  Using logic analogous to 'parse_chessmetrics-profiles_full.py',
  make code for stepwise scraping of succesive top players list, as follows:
 0) Analyze starting "Monthly List" page source, stored as '~/data/chessmetrics _ Monthly_1843-01.htm'
 (originally from URL:
 http://chessmetrics.com/cm/CM2/SingleMonth.asp?Params=184010SSSSS5S113454184301151000005300000210100
 ) - to establish, for the algo to construct, data link constrauction of the underlying pages!
 1) for the #1 player there, retrieve its "Chessmetrics Player Profile", in this instance 
 'http://chessmetrics.com/cm/CM2/PlayerProfile.asp?Params=184030SSSSS5S023538184301151000005300000210100'
 2) add to the final output data from the lines shown, where the player was #1, in CSV format:
  1. col "LastName, FirstName"
  2. col YYYY-MM for the rating list date
  3. col URL for rating list 
  4. col rating
  5. col rank
  Add one more line, for the first time this player was no longer #1
  
 For the first stage of this programming task, stop here - have '~/data/test2.csv" saved
 
 >>	program stopped w/o output!
 
 ___
 OK, the initial testing code 'parse_chessmetrics-reigning1.py' worked correctly.
 Now, move onto next stage of this programming task: proceed for stepwise scraping of succesive top players list
 (with 'parse_chessmetrics-reigning_succesive.py')!
 From the prior result, take the link for the first time the previous reigning top player was no longer #1 -
  in this first instance, 'http://chessmetrics.com/cm/CM2/SingleMonth.asp?Params=184010SSSSS5S023538184305151000005300000210100'.
 Loop through processing, as
 1) for the #1 player there, retrieve its "Chessmetrics Player Profile", in this instance 
 2) add to the final output data from the lines shown, where the player was #1, in CSV format:
  1. col "LastName, FirstName"
  2. col YYYY-MM for the rating list date
  3. col URL for rating list 
  4. col rating
  5. col rank
  +Add one more line, for the first time this player was no longer #1

>>  Make a limited test version, where the run is stopped after getting 3 reigning players

>> change initialization to saved webpage '~/data/chessmetrics _ Monthly_1843-01.htm', instead of an online starting

>>  Very good - see output created, uploaded.

Now next stage of this programming task:
write a version that can restart successive runs - cmd-line param1 would have the CSV line from a previous run,
 and cmd-line param1 is the new MAX_REIGNS for a reaterted one; the new program would take 'Rating List URL'
 from the last record read in. Otherwise the scraping logic would remain.
 Form output filename as '~/data/chessmetrics-reigning_Date1-Date2.csv',
 where Date1 and Date2 are the first and last montly list date included.
 
>> So, the logic used so far got derailed when players ranking got reversed over time;
need a more sophisticated approach! Step through the montly top-5 lists, instead.
See source code from the uploaded HTML 'chessmetrics _ Monthly_1843-01.htm'.
The code would access this as '~/data/chessmetrics _ Monthly_1843-01.htm'.
From each such page retrieved, make a single CSV record in the output file, 
with data for all top 5 players:
  1. col YYYY-MM for the rating list date
  2. col URL for rating list 
 followed by 4 fields for #1 player
  3. col "LastName, FirstName"
  4. col rating
  5. col rank
  6. col URL for player's profile
	this is reconstructed from the page, according to this template:
	<SCRIPT LANGUAGE=JAVASCRIPT>
 function LinkPlayer(NewPlayerID)
 {
  var x = NewPlayerID + "";
  var y = "000000" + x;
  NewPlayerID = y.substr(y.length-6,6);

  var NewURL = "PlayerProfile.asp?Params=184010SSSSS5S" + NewPlayerID + "184301151000005300000210100";
  location.href = NewURL;
 }
	Note this would vary page-by-page, for different months.
 followed by 4 fields each for #2-#5 players.
 After this, reconstruct from the page the link to next month, according to this template:
 function LinkAge(NewAgeInMonths)
 {
  var NewURL = "SingleAge.asp?Params=184010SSSSS5S113454184301151000005300000210" + NewAgeInMonths;
  location.href = NewURL;
 }
 
 Then retrieve that list, after a random delay between 1.1 and 2.9 seconds.
 Redo the analysis for that monthly list, then repeat until a specified maximum (cmd-par2, or default of 99) is reached.
 Make the program restartable: cmd-par1 would specifiy CSV output from a previous run; its last record (URL in 3. field)
  would be the 1st monthly list starting this run. If no cmd-line parameters are given, then the program reverts to the stored 
 '~/data/chessmetrics _ Monthly_1843-01.htm' for initialization.  
 
 Your completed code should be listed in full as a response (NOT put onto Canvas)!
 